Someone here make a call?
这里的人打电话向他们要我么?
Nope.
不是
They dropped you on psych, Jim.
他们刷了你 因为心理测试不过关 吉姆
You blew their profiles.
你的心理曲线图乱套了
We're all a little goofy here.
我们这里的人都有点笨
You'd rather be with us, wouldn't you?
你宁肯帮我们干 不是吗?
Absolutely, sir.
当然 先生
Good answer.
说的真好
Have a seat.
请坐
Said you were bilingual on your app.
申请书上说你会两国语言
They want to test your Spanish.
他们想测你的西班牙语
We can get that going if you got time.
如果你有时间 我们可以测一下
Yes. Sure.
当然有
Who's "they"?
他们是谁?
Your fans upstairs.
你的粉丝 在楼上
Fans upstairs? Who?
楼上的粉丝? 是谁？
This is some shit above my pay grade,
那个比我的等级高的人才知道
but some very important people have an eye on you, Jim.
一些重要人物正盯着你 吉姆
Westside Realty Management.
西区房地产公司
How may I direct your call?
你要我转给谁?
Please hold.
请稍等
Okay, Mike...
好 迈克...
Alonzo?
阿努左?
Oh, shit. Joe?!
噢 乔?!
Damn...! What's up, dog?
妈的...! 你好啊 兄弟?
- Mikey, look at you. - What are you doing here, dude?
- 迈克 你看你 - 你在这干吗?
Mikey, man, check you out.
迈克 看看你
What the fuck you doing here?
你在这里干吗?
Fucking grew up. I work here.
在这长大 我在这工作
- Get out of here. - Yeah.
- 真的假的 - 是啊
Dude, you got to come on up.
兄弟 你得上去走走
Yeah, I'll show you the office.
我带你看办公室
Fuck, you're gonna trip, man,
你会大吃一惊 兄弟
I can see the ocean and everything.
我能看到海和所有东西
Check you out, fucking ocean view and all that.
你看你 海上风景都来了
You're wearing a suit now.
你现在都穿西装了
- Got your hair cut. - Hey, watch out, baby.
- 理了头发 - 嘿 小心 宝贝
Yeah. Tag no more, huh?
碰都不行 哈?
No, man.
不 哥们
Dude, what's up with your brother, Pedro?
哥们 你兄弟派德罗还好吗?
Oh, man, he's in Iraq. He's in a forward unit.
噢 他在伊拉克前方部队里
Get the fuck out of here. Yeah.
不会吧
Fuckin' Mexicans.
该死的墨西哥人
Bye, sweetie.
再见 甜心
Thank you, sir. I need me some of this, man.
谢谢你 先生 我正需要这个
I've been taking piss all day.
我每天都在忍受
Dude!
哥们!
What?
什么?
You're not going to
你不会
- fucking believe this. - What?
- 相信这个 - 什么?
- I had an interview today. - Yeah?
- 我今天有个面试 - 是吗?
- Remember Crazy Joe? - Yeah, yeah, yeah.
- 还记得疯狂乔吗? - 记得
Dude stomped that guy's face in at Taco Land
在泰克兰他踩那家伙的脸
for grabbing his chick's ass.
因为那人摸他马子的屁股
Homeboy got his shit together, man.
他闯出个名堂来了
Went to UCLA.
去了加州大学洛杉矶分校
Works at this office up in Century City.
在这里上班
I got the hookup, dog.
我有人给我牵线了
- 12 an hour. - Hoo-hoo!
- 每小时12块 - 呼 呼!
- That's a lot of lettuce. - That's right.
- 大笔的钞票 - 对
And in three months, I get benefits.
三个月后 我还能拿到救济金
Damn! Benefits?
什么! 救济金?
- Yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah. - Shit!
- 是的 - 妈的!
Yeah!
是的!
It's not for sure yet, though, dude.
只是还没有定下来
I still got to meet the owner, right.
我还要去见老板
But he says I'm straight.
可他说我很诚实
It's all good, you know.
十有八九成了 你知道的
You're in. Dude...
你成功了 哥们...
I'm in. Oh, shit.
我成功了 噢 该死
Yeah... What happened?
是... 怎么了?
They want my ass, man. Going back tomorrow
他们要我 明天我去
for a polygraph test.
做个谎言测试
If I pass that, they'll send me to Georgia next week.
如果过了 下周他们就派我去 乔治亚州
Oh...! Damn! It's like that?!
噢...! 真好! 真那样吗?!
What's up, lawman?
你好吗 警官?
Whoo-hoo!
呼 呼!
How you gonna pass a lie detector test,
你怎么通过谎言测试
- you lying motherfucker? - Aw, easy, man.
- 你个骗人的混蛋? - 噢 很容易 哥们
After every question, you just fucking squeeze
回答完问题 你就象是挤了半天
like you're taking a dump, you know, man.
终于把废物排出体外
- It throws the machine off. Ooh! - Oh, dog.
- 把心里的压抑排除 噢! - 噢 哥们
You're gonna shit your pants like that, bro.
你会拉在裤子里面
Fuck, I think I just did.
该死 我想我刚才就拉了
All right, Jim,
好了 吉姆
I'm going to ask you some control questions
我会问你一些问题
before we get to the good stuff.
然后进入主题
They can be answered just "yes" or "no."
你只需回答是或不是
Just relax and respond naturally.
放松 自然的回答就行
Are you ready?
准备好了没?
Yes, sir.
好了 先生
You can just answer "yes" or "no."
你可以只回答是或不是
"Is your name Jim Luther Davis?"
"你叫 吉姆 卢瑟 戴维斯吗?"
Yes.
是
"Do you live in Los Angeles?"
"你住在洛杉矶吗?"
"Are you 26 years old?"
"你26岁了?"
Yes.
是
"Are you married?"
"你结婚了？"
No.
没有
"Are you wearing shoes?"
"你穿了鞋吗?"
Yes.
是
"Have you ever smoked marijuana?"
"你吸过大麻吗?"
"Aside from the occasion you mentioned in your application?"
"除去你在申请书里写到的那几次?"
No.
没有
Jim, knock it off.
吉姆 少来了
What, sir?
什么 先生?
Son, I've been doing polygraph examinations
孩子 在你还在老爸的巢里时
since you were swimming in your daddy's balls.
我就开始做这个测试了
So I know all the tricks.
所以我知道所有的把戏
You've either got a tack in your shoe
要么是你鞋子放了个钉子
or you're clinching your butt.
要么就是在挤自己的屁股
I've got spikes all over this thing.
我这边跳得很厉害
If you do it again,
如果你再这么做
I'm going to void this test
我就不做测试了
and report that you were uncooperative.
说你不合作
Do you understand?
你明白吗?
Yes, sir.
明白 先生
Walk with me.
跟我来
We've got a problem, Jim.
我们遇到问题了 吉姆
With what?
什么问题?
With your candor.
你的坦白
Come in.
进来
He's here, sir.
他来了
Bring him in.
带他进来
Jim, this is Mr. Hollenbeck, our regional director.
吉姆 这是荷文贝克先生 我们的地区负责人
Pleased to meet you, sir.
很高兴见到你 先生
Have a seat.
请坐
Mr. Gillespie.
格斯皮先生
Pleased to meet you, sir.
很高兴见到你 先生
Jim, uh...
吉姆 呃...
you're an exemplary candidate
你是个值得推荐的候选人
with valuable operational experience.
有宝贵的军事行动经验
You've cleared the psych and physical hurdles.
你已经没有心理和身体障碍
Your credit's good, you've kept your nose clean,
你的信誉良好 不沾毒品
you've got the Spanish.
又会说西班牙语
You clearance is still valid.
你的证明书仍然有效
Everybody we talked to for background
每个人一谈起你
had only great things to say about you.
都是大加赞赏
And then you scored a negative-five on the polygraph.
可接着你测慌考试得了个负5分
That's indicative of deception.
说明你撒谎了
We were wondering why
我们一直想知道为什么
until we got the results of urinalysis.
直到我们得到了尿检的结果
We detected THC metabolites in the urine, Jim.
我们查了大麻 吉姆
Levels were just below the positive threshold,
含量刚好低于正常值
but there was a presence.
可是还是有这种成分存在
Do you have a drug problem, Mr. Davis?
你有毒品问题吗 戴维斯?
I don't have a drug problem, sir.
我没有 先生
I made a very stupid mistake.
我犯错了
Would you care to tell us the circumstances
能告诉我们你犯错的
of your stupid mistake?
情况吗?
I was at a party...
我去了个派对
and someone offered me a joint.
别人给我一小卷
I was pretty angry about not getting into
我很生气 因为进不了
the LAPD, so I was feeling rebellious and, uh...
警察局 我有点叛逆
...I inhaled.
我就吸了
Someone considering a career in law enforcement
有人说 要在法律执行部门做事
would be well advised to exercise
你必须学会
a little more discipline.
控制好自己
Yes, sir.
是的 先生
I'm on the fence, Doug.
我还犹豫不决 道格
It's your call.
你来决定
Mr. Davis, I'm in charge of several programs.
戴维斯先生 我正负责几个军事项目
Yes, sir?
是的 先生?
Had a nice chat with your old commanding officer.
跟老指挥官好好聊聊
Good.
很好
Recognize these guys?
认识这些人吗?
Huh? Yeah,
哈? 是啊
they're your buddies.
他们是你的朋友
Your old Hajji buddies.
你的老中东地区的朋友
You should work in a deli how you sliced these guys up.
看你是怎么把他们切成一片一片的 你该去熟食店工作
Jesus Christ.
天啊
Oh, I'm sorry.
哦 不好意思
Did I ruin your lunch?
我倒你胃口了么?
You went through those sons of bitches
你就这样残忍的杀害
like butter.
那些狗娘养的
I took my objective
我干掉目标
and did what was necessary
做了我必须做的
to obtain information vital to national security
来获取到对国家安全至关重要的情报
that saved American lives.
然后拯救了美国民众
Whacked them all, huh, Jim?
把他们全干掉了 哈 吉姆?
My C.O. told me not to leave anything breathing.
上级告诉我不留任何活口
- I do what I'm told. - Relax, son.
- 我做了我被吩咐做的 - 放松 孩子
You were getting paid to fuck people up.
你拿着薪水去搞砸别人
You know we're beefing up our anti-narcotics programs
你知道我们的反毒行动正加派人手吗？
in Latin America.
在拉丁美洲
Yes, sir.
知道 先生
I had heard some things on the grapevine.
我听到一些小道消息
I want you on my team.
我想你加入我们组
I need someone who can get things done
我需要能完成任务的人
on my task force in Colombia.
加入我在哥伦比亚的特遣部队
Sir...
先生
I listed Los Angeles and San Diego on my dream sheet.
我最想去的是洛杉矶和圣地亚哥
No slots in southern California?
南加州没有职位吗?
No, Jim.
没了 吉姆
I got Colombia.
我有哥伦比亚
That's what I have for you.
只能给你这个
If it's not what you want,
如果你不想要
thank you for your time.
谢谢你的时间
You can hit the door.
你可以走人了
What exactly would I be doing?
准确的讲 要我去干什么事?
Running and gunning in the jungle?
在丛林里打游击吗?
Mr. Davis, this is the deal.
戴维斯先生 是这样的
You'll be riding shotgun with the locals
你携枪和当地的
as interpreter-advisor on sharp end operations.
翻译顾问参与突击行动
You'll be in some very hot areas.
你将去很火地方
How hot?
怎样火?
We talking trigger time?
你在和我说一触即发吗?
Sure, if you want.
当然 如果你想去
Well, who exactly would I be working for?
我到底为谁工作?
The U.S. government, Jim.
美国政府 吉姆.
I want you in Glynco, Georgia next week.
我希望你下周去乔治亚州 格林
You make it through in one piece,
你能活着完成任务
you'll be working Colombia's finest by the summer.
夏天你就能当上警察
It's just that...
只是
I'm supposed to get married, sir.
我应该结婚 先生
Maybe now is not the time to start a family.
或许现在不是成家的时候
We've been together a long time.
我们在一起很久了
I'm serious about marrying her.
我非常想娶她 认真的
Foreign bride could jeopardize your security clearance.
外国老婆会危害你的忠诚度
Jim, don't shack up with some Mexican.
吉姆 别和墨西哥人搞上了
Colombian broads are smoking hot and knee deep.
哥伦比亚的女人火的很 而且很配合
You get a per diem and a driver.
你有出差津贴和司机
You'll live like a fucking king down there.
在那边你可以过得象个国王一样
Yes, sir, I understand.
是的 我懂了
You take some time,
你花点时间
think about what you want to do.
想想怎么做
This is a serious commitment.
这是重大的使命
I want the opportunity, sir.
我想要这个机会
I want on board.
我想加入
Welcome aboard.
欢迎
I'm taking a big chance on you.
我对你寄予厚望
Thank you, sir.
谢谢你
This is the career I've dreamed of.
这是我梦寐以求的职业
These are your orders,
这是给你的命令
orientation material and travel money.
相关资料和旅游费用
Report to FLETC before the end of working hours Wednesday.
在周三上班时间结束前 去联邦法律执行训练中心报道
Thank you, sir.
谢谢
God.
走吧
Sorry, dog.
抱歉
I got the job.
我得到工作了
Oh, shit.
噢 该死
Yeah?
是吗?
Me, too.
我也是
- When do you start? - Monday.
- 你什么时候上班? - 星期一
When do you start?
你呢？
Wednesday.
周三
Big Jim, back on the man's payroll.
我的吉姆兄又回到薪水册上了
Got the W-2
拿到了工资
and the employee handbook as proof of employment.
和雇员手册 作为被雇的证明
I will be back in the arms of my woman tonight.
我今晚又要投入我女人的怀抱了
Good.
好
Hey, we got to celebrate this shit.
我们该庆祝
Salud.
干杯
Oh, shit.
噢 妈的
Fuzz.
警察
They're on my ass, dog.
跟屁虫
And my license is suspended.
我的驾照被吊销了
Yeah, maybe he's after someone else.
也许他在追另外的人
Shit. Fucking shit, man.
该死的
He's pointing right at me.
他正指着我
And we got the open beers.
我们在喝酒
Fuck the beers, the guns.
去他妈的酒 枪
Shoot the fucker.
杀了他
Car's in my name. We're fucked.
车注册的是我的名字 我们完了
Shit. Right when shit was starting to go good, dude,
妈的 刚是晴天 又见乌云 哥们
I'm going to jail.
我要坐牢了
Damn it, I'm going to jail.
该死的 我要坐牢了
I can dump these guys.
我可以解决他们
Rip the video from their trunk.
销掉他们车尾箱的录象
Let's see them hands.
给我看你的手
on the fucking dash!
放到仪表板上!
Grab the sky or I'll blow your fucking heads off.
手举起来 不然我会敲下你的头
Blink and die, scumbags.
一眨眼就死了 坏蛋
Oh.
噢
Look who it is, dude.
看看是谁
It's all right, I know these guys.
没事了 我认识
You fucking asshole.
你个混蛋
You're such a prick. You scared the fuck out of me.
鸡巴 吓死我了
What's up, homie?
你好吗 伙计?
- What's up, fool? - What's up, man.
- 你好 傻瓜? - 你好 哥们
I almost shot you, jerk.
我差点开枪了
That shit wasn't fucking funny, Leo.
这一点都不有趣 李
Yeah, it was hilarious.
是 是场闹剧
You guys getting fucked up?
你们搞砸了?
Of course, dog, it's Friday.
当然 今天周五
Well, Boot, you in the Academy yet?
你进警察局没?
Fuck no.
没
Fuck the LAPD.
去他妈的洛城警局
It's local small-time bullshit.
地方的三流机构
I'm going with the feds.
我跟联邦局的混
How'd you get that hook-up, dog?
你怎么找到关系的?
You know, me, got my connects, you know.
你知道 有关系
Going to FLETC on Wednesday.
周三汇报给联邦法律执行训练中心
Hey, see you can get me in there.
嘿 看能把我也弄进去不
Yeah, I'll look into that.
我会考虑的
How's Sylvia?
西尔维亚还好吗?
None of your concern, ass wipe.
不是你该关心的 檫屁纸
Say hi to her for me, no?
替我向她问好 不行吗?
No.
不
This vato's all protective of his female.
这哥们对她的女人保护有佳
Check this out.
看看这个
Nice, huh?
漂亮吧?
It's a nine? Uh-huh.
漂亮哈？ 呃呵
Sorry, dog, I got a lot of nines.
我有很多9毫米的
Come on, dude, it's a bad-ass Ruger.
拜托 这是挺好的罗格枪
Talk to Toussaint. He'll buy that shit.
去和土沙谈 他会买
Toussaint, he's... he's in Florida.
土沙 他... 他在佛罗里达
He's back. He called me today.
他回来了 今天还打电话给我了
Page me tonight, bro.
今晚呼叫我 兄弟
We'll hit the clubs and tear up some fine hinas.
我们去夜总会找马子爽
Later. Sure, dog.
再见 好
I'm on the City's time.
我还要巡逻
You guys be cool.
你们保重
Okay?
好吗?
That fuck-- he put a scare in me.
该死的吓了我一大跳
Yeah, me, too.
是 我也是
He's a dick.
他是个鸡巴
Want to party with him?
想和他聚会吗?
See if this motherfucker's home, dude.
看这个混蛋在家不
Toussaint? Toussaint?!
土沙? 土沙?!
Yo, Toussaint?
土沙?
Yeah, come on, man.
出来啊 哥们
Can't go far in that little fucking place of yours.
不能进你的小屋了
Goddammit, I'm coming.
该死的 我来了
Chill out.
冷静
Washing that dirty ass.
洗屁屁了
Damn it.
该死的
Group love. Group... Come on.
聚会快乐 聚会
Group love, boys.
聚会快乐
Welcome back, hometown.
欢迎回来 家乡
Hey, I missed you crazy fuckers, man.
嘿 我想你们疯子啊
Leo told us you were back.
李说你回来了
Thanks for calling asshole.
谢谢你打电话 混蛋
You a cop?
你是警察?
Uh-uh. Going federal.
去联邦局
Man, craziest head I know
我知道的最疯狂的想法
is going
就是
to be a fed.
去联邦局
Yes, sir! Sir.
是的 先生! 先生
Still sponging off your woman?
还依赖着你老婆?
Fuck you, dog. I got a job.
去你的 我有工作了
This motherfucker.
这个混蛋
Look, dude.
看 哥们
This is bad.
很不错
It's yours for three big ones, dog.
300块就是你的了
Fuck yeah, I want it.
我想要
What's up?
你好?
Huh?
哈?
What the fuck you say now, huh?
你现在说什么 哈?
Hey. Huh?
嘿 哈？
Bam, bam, bam.
砰 砰
Motherfucker, I'm strapped.
混蛋 我身无分文
What the fuck is up now, huh?
现在怎么样 哈?
Whoo-ooh!
唔 呵!
Whoa, whoa.
哇
Your kneecap and shit.
两膝中弹
Step up and get blasted.
过来找死
Shit, man, what the fuck is up now?
妈的 现在怎样?
Hey, kick back, gunslinger.
嘿 冷静 歹徒
It's loaded.
上了膛的
That shit goes through walls.
能穿墙
You pop the neighbor's little kids.
你会杀掉隔壁的小孩
Uh-oh.
啊
Ooh.
噢
Fuck, dude.
妈的 哥们
Whoa, I'm straight, bro.
哇 我有点子 兄弟
Yo, guys, we got to party tonight, you know?
我们去开派对 知道吗?
Go clubbin' or something.
去夜总会
I got a better idea.
我有更好的主意
What?
什么?
Here, sir.
这里 先生
Let's go to Mexico.
我们去墨西哥
Mexico?!
墨西哥?!
- Yeah. - I'm in.
- 对 - 我也去
Only fags like that...
只有这样的香烟...
Because you're a little faggot.
因为你是个小变态
I don't get it, too much fucking hills.
我不理解 这么多山
Right, right.
对
Dude, yo, dude, stay back boy, stay back.
哥们 止步 止步
Motherfucker's got to ask permission.
混蛋要征求同意
Fuck you, all right?
去你的 好不?
Let me tell you something.
让我和你说
I am a grown motherfucking man, all right?
我是个大男人 好不?
I'm going to tell her the good news,
我去报喜
make up, grab my shit and we are out.
找个理由 拿我的东西 我们开溜
Lines, lines, and more lines.
可卡因 更多的可卡因
For many passengers traveling through LAX,
这么多人穿越边界
the waiting has become unbearable.
等待不能忍受
It's hit or miss, you can't predict it...
能蒙混过关或失手 你无法预测
Excuse me, you're not made out of glass.
抱歉 你不是玻璃做的
I'm made out of me.
我就是我
You're drunk.
你醉了
I'm celebrating, baby.
我来庆祝 宝贝
What, another wasted day?
什么 又一个浪费的日子?
Here.
给你
...security since 9-11, but that's true everywhere.
...9-11以来到处戒备 哪里都一样
...and still a recent study shows the wait at LAX
可是仍然有个研究显示 在边界等待的队伍
is the third longest in the world...
是世界第三长的
This is a good company.
这是个好公司
They make all the new condos downtown.
市区公寓大多是他们在出售
How much?
多少?
$12 an hour.
一小时12块
Plus their MIS guy
在加上有个无能的家伙
is leaving in three months.
三个月后离开
I'm going to update my certifications
我会更新自己的职位
and take his job over.
接他的班
Then I'll make bank.
我就能赚大比钞票
Such an asshole.
该死的混蛋
What? Why? This shit is real.
什么? 为什么? 真的
This is a great job, the pay is outstanding
是个极好的工作 好高的薪水
and it's a great opportunity for me to do what I want to do.
是我最好的机会去做自己想做的事
I know.
我知道
It's so... it's so Mike, you know.
很迈克
You can't just go out and get a shitty job.
你不能出去找个很差的工作
You gotta... you gotta get a...
你必须找个...
A dream job?
梦想的工作?
Yeah, a dream job.
对 梦想的工作.
Well, why shouldn't your dream guy have a dream job?
为什么你梦中情人不能得到梦想中的工作?
Come here, I have a job for you.
来吧 有个活要你来干
What the fuck is taking so long?
怎么这么久?
I knew this shit would happen.
就知道会这样
She hates my ass.
她恨死我了
She's not going to let him go.
她不会让他走
Go knock.
去敲门
Bro, drag his fucking ass out of there.
把他屁股拉出来
Yo, Miguel.
迈克
Hey.
嘿
Mike, hurry up.
迈克 快点
Yo, what the fuck are you doing?
你在干吗?
Come on, dude.
快点
Dog, I'm tearin' it up, man.
我在做爱
I'm hittin' it, bro. It's been a few days.
我在干她 很久没干了
You guys just go ahead, man. I'm gonna chill.
你们先走 我冷静一下
What?
什么?
I'm just gonna kick it here with the woman.
我想和我女人亲密一下
You said you'd go, man.
你说的你要去的 哥们
Your woman's in your head.
你脑子里全是她
That's wrong.
这不对
She's got your nuts, bro.
她抓住你的心了
Dog, dog...
兄弟...
Sylvia's all happy 'cause I got a job, all right, dude?
西尔维亚高兴是因为我找到工作了 对吗?
She wants us to fuckin' chill together.
她想我们好好庆祝一下
Man, that girl put the zap on your head.
那女人迷住你了
This is our last chance to hang.
这是我们最后兜风的机会
- You're like my brother. - Yeah.
- 你就象是我的亲兄弟 - 对
You're all I got. You're gonna dog me like that?
你是我的全部 你就这样逃避我啊?
I ain't no fucking do...
我不会...
How are you, baby?
你好 宝贝?
Hey, Sylvia, he's going to Mexico.
嘿  西尔维亚 他要去墨西哥
No, he isn't, Jim. Yes, he is.
不 他不去 吉姆. 是的 他去
I'm joining the feds. I'm gone, I'm out of here next week.
我去联邦局 我要走了 下周就走
The least you can do
你至少可以
is let my best friend
让我最好的朋友
see me off.
送我一程
Baby, it's not safe.
宝贝 不安全
All you're going to do is drink.
你要去做的就是喝酒
Aw, fuck, man.
啊 该死的
Mike, come on.
迈克 拜托
Come on, fuck, man!
来吧 哥们!
Come on, you promised.
拜托了 你答应过的
You promised, man.
你答应过的 哥们
Yo... I promised, Sylvia, okay?
我答应过的 西尔维亚  好不?
Mike, you're not going to Mexico.
迈克 你不要去
What?
什么?
You're not going.
你不要去
I'm not your fucking puppet, Sylvia.
我可不是你的傀儡 西尔维亚
All right, you know what, do what you want.
好吧  知道吗 去做你想做的吧
But I'm not going to be here when you get back.
回来时我不会在这里了
That's fucked up.
乱套了
Why you got to lay that bullshit on him?
你为啥限制他?
Because I don't want him going with you, Jim.
因为我不想他和你一起去 吉姆
You're fucking nuts.
你疯了
You're crazy and you're dangerous,
你疯了 而且很危险
and my biggest nightmare is you with a fucking badge.
你是我最大的梦魇
You're the last person who should have one.
他最不该和你在一起
Yeah? Yeah.
是吗? 是
That's not bullshit, it's the truth.
不是胡说 是事实
Fuck this!
操!
Whoa, wait.
哇 等等
Whatever, man.
不管怎样 哥们
Fuckin' thanks, homie!
谢谢
Yeah, laters.
是 再见
Bye.
再见
Yo, yo.
喂
I'm going.
我去
I gotta go.
我必须去
Get the fuck out of here, go!
滚开 去!
Go!
去啊!
Fuck this shit, man.
妈的
Good night, Sylvia.
晚安 西尔维亚
Kiss my ass, Jim.
亲我屁股 吉姆
Oh, any time, sellout.
噢 什么时候都行 我亲个够
Oh, you going to be happy once he's dead? Huh?
噢 要是他死了你会高兴吗? 哈?
Hey, Toussaint.
嘿 土沙.
I heard the battle, man.
我听到吵架了
Yo, your lady didn't want you going, huh?
你老婆不让你去 哈?
No, but I'm going.
不 可是我要去
- Hell, yeah. - Shit.
- 妈的 是啊 - 该死的
- I'm a motherfucking man. - That's right.
- 我是个混蛋 - 对
Shit. I walk the Earth at will.
妈的 我要玩转地球
- Damn right. - I do whatever the fuck I want.
- 对极了 - 想做什么 就做什么
You know, we're men, right?
知道不 我们是男人 对不？
- We're men, right? - That's right.
- 我们是男人 对吗? - 对
That's what we do, right?
我们就这么做 对吧?
Amen. And don't worry--
阿门 别担心
home girl will be right there waiting when you get back.
你回来的时候 你老婆在家乖乖的等着
You're right. You're right.
你说的对
She wouldn't play that shit like that.
她不会和我玩失踪
Shit, I got a fucking job for real.
我真的找到工作了
You did.
是的
Plus you're my homie, dog. You're my homie.
而且你是我死党 你是我死党
You're going to go fucking do your thing
你会去爽一把 做你该做的
- and this is it. - No, shit, dude.
- 就这样 - 不 妈的 哥们
Yo, we're all dogs.
我们都是好朋友
I got you guys back, man.
我有你们支持着我
No doubt, no doubt.
毫无疑问
It's just going to be fucking cool, yo.
肯定会很酷
I got a job, you got a job.
我找到工作了
Shit, I got some bud.
妈的 我有些大麻
- We got some smokes. - We got some
- 我们有烟草 - 我们有
- motherfucking money. - We are on a mission.
- 钱 - 我们要完成任务
Let's get our heads together so we can achieve our objective
我们齐聚一心 就能尽快
in a timely manner.
达成目标
Let's get deployed, people.
我们大干一场
Wake up, wake up, wake up.
醒来
Rise and fucking shine.
起来 太阳晒屁股了
Come on, ladies. Chow time.
快点 娘娘腔 开餐了
Chow's getting cold.
菜都快冷了
- Oh, what the fuck, Jim? - Chill, dude.
- 噢 怎么搞的 吉姆? - 冷静 哥们
Dude, where are we?
我们在哪?
Family, man.
家啊
Damn! It's a shizzack...
该死! 好破啊
Hey, hey, hey, hey.
嘿
It's a home, all right?
是个家 好不?
Respect, bro.
放尊重点 兄弟
Straighten up, fellas.
打起精神 朋友们
My old lady, Marta.
我老情人  玛特
Hola.
你好
Mike. Hola, mucho gusto.
迈克 你好 很高兴见到你
Hola, Mike. Toussaint.
你好 迈克 土沙
Hola. Hola. Hola.
你好
Hola. Marisa.
你好 玛日莎
Buenos dias. Mi mama.
早上好 我妈妈
Mucho gusto. Marta's mom.
很高兴见到你 玛特的妈妈
Buenos dias.
早安
Vicki.
维基
La prima, esa es mi prima.
我堂姐
Mucho gusto.
早安 很高兴见到你
Mucho gusto. Mike. Vicki.
很高兴见到你 迈克 维基
Toussaint.
土沙
Vicki.
维基
Okay.
好了
Hey, grab yourselves a rock.
找个石板凳做
S? por favor, sientense.
请坐
Vicki?
维基?
¿Caf? quieren caf?
喝咖啡吗？
S? caf? por favor. Vicki, andale.
维基 倒咖啡来
Tranquila, baby.
镇静宝贝
¡Mama!
妈!
Yeah, w-what's she saying, dude?
是啊 她说什么 哥们?
Oh, they... they think you're cool.
他们认为你很酷
Oh, sweet.
噢 真甜
Aqu?tienes. Gracias.
谢谢
- Caliente. - Thank you.
- 热身的 - 谢谢
Dude...
哥们...
Marta's fine as fuck, bro.
玛特很漂亮
Hey, hey, hey...
嘿
I'm just saying, dude. You need to marry her, bro.
我是说 你要娶她
If you don't, you're a fool.
如果不 你就是傻瓜
¿Que dice?
他说什么?
Oh...
噢...
Oh, that shit's good, man.
噢 好极了
No shit, you know they got that good fucking weed from here.
很棒 这烟草棒极了
That's what I want. Some of that good shit.
正是我想要的 一些这样的好东西
You know where some fields are or something, Jim?
你知道哪里有地吗 吉姆?
Yeah, that's not... I want to see, like, where they grow it.
我想看他们把这玩意种在哪里
You know, and then maybe
你知道 可能
they'll let us go out and, like, pick some.
他们会让我们出去自己摘一些来
You know, pick some of that really good weed.
摘一些好的烟草
Shit.
该死
Toussaint?
土沙?
This is nice.
很好
This is beautiful, man.
很漂亮
Dog, you see this?
哥们  你看到没?
Here.
这里
Mmm...
恩..
Beautiful...
多美啊...
Man!
天!
Mmm!
恩!
When the hell'd you get all the pistos, dog?
什么时候拿到这些酒的?
Mexico, man.
墨西哥
It's magic.
变魔术
He bleed?
他捞了一大笔钱?
Like a stuffed pig.
象个吃饱了的猪
How'd Letty know you were tearing up her sister?
莱蒂怎么知道你在搞她妹妹?
That fuckin' bitch Patti, right?
那个婊子帕迪 是吧?
- Ah... - I took her to dinner.
- 啊... - 我带她去吃饭
Took her for a cruise up to Malibu, you know?
带着她开车兜风去了马里布 知道吗?
Got up all in it. Back of my ride...
在那玩了个痛快 回到车里...
Pounded that fish, man.
干了那条鱼
Good fuckin' fish.
好爽的鱼
I figured the crazy broad
我想那疯狂婆娘
pulled out some hairs and pubes
一定扯下几把头发和阴毛
and stashed it in the seat, you know?
藏在座位下面 你知道吗?
Oh, dude, you got to watch that shit, man.
噢 你得去看看
Chicks get treacherous.
女人也奸诈
Yeah, no shit. Sibling rivalry, Jim.
是 当然 姐妹间的竞争 吉姆
Next day,
第二天
I'm driving around with Letty all kick back and shit,
我载莱蒂兜风 约会
and she radars in on this rat's nest, man.
然后她发现了那撮乱毛
Pulls out these long-ass hairs, she's like "What are these?"
拉出长长的毛 问 这是什么?
"Whose are these?"
"这些是谁的?"
She sees all the pubes mixed in, man... fuckin' busted.
她看到那些阴毛混成一团 他妈的荡妇
Busted!
荡妇!
Oh!
噢!
Dude, how'd she know they were her sister's?
她怎么知道是她妹的？
Oh, come on, dude.
噢 拜托
Mexican chick voodoo, right, Mike?
墨西哥女人会巫术 对吧  迈克?
You know, live and learn.
你知道 活着并学习
Yep, next time you'll be all up in your ride
下次你就会和某个
with the Super Vac, dude. Treachery!
巫婆在车里乱来了 奸诈!
Yep, treachery.
是的 奸诈
Um...
哦...
shouldn't we be
我们不应该
helping them?
帮帮她们吗?
You know how to hand wash?
你知道怎么洗衣吗?
- No. - Then don't sweat it.
- 不知 - 那就别担心
Yeah, we're men.
是 我们是男人
They know we don't do that shit.
他们知道我们不做那种事
That's right.
对
We're men.
我们是男人
Oh, yeah!
噢 对!
This is paradise, huh?
这是天堂 哈?
Mm-hmm.
恩
Yo, Mike?
迈克?
Yeah?
什么?
They're sending me to Colombia.
他们派我去哥伦比亚
Colombia.
哥伦比亚
Who, the man?
谁 老板?
Yep.
对
They're tearing shit up down there, they need my help.
他们在那铲除邪恶 需要我帮忙
Doing what?
帮什么忙?
Busting up drug labs and drug lords
扫荡吸毒场所和贩毒的团伙
- and all that shit. - You got it.
- 那样的狗屁事 - 说的对
Gonna be an advisor, you know-- shoot him, him and him.
做个顾问-- 杀他 杀他 他
Then it's back to the barracks for bitches and beer.
然后回到兵营找马子喝啤酒
I'm set.
我都准备好了
Why do you want to do that shit, dude?
你为啥想做这些狗屁事 哥们?
I mean...
我的意思是...
what about Marta, you know?
玛特怎么办 你知道吗?
Ain't gonna happen.
那不会发生
They told me not to get married.
他们要我别结婚
That's messed.
那很糟
They really told you that?
他们真告诉你这个?
Not straight up, but I heard 'em.
并不是很直白 我听到他们说
Yo, if the feds won't let you hook up with your old lady,
如果那帮人不让你和爱人结婚
you need to tell them to fuck off.
你得要他们滚
Yeah, I mean,
我是说
you love her, she loves you, right?
你喜欢她 他喜欢你 对吧?
Dude, you need to move down here, marry Marta,
你得搬到这里来 娶玛特
you know, get a good-ass job
找个好工作
working with fucking tourists or something.
做个导游之类的
Fuck that.
去他的
Taking bucket baths in cold-ass water?
在冷水里用桶子洗澡?
You know, wading around in ankle-deep mud?
在深及踝部的泥巴地里跋涉?
Outhouses, man!
拓荒 哥们!
Fuckin' outhouses!
去他妈的拓荒!
You told Marta yet?
你告诉玛特了没?
You love this place.
你喜欢这地方
It's in your eyes, man.
从你的眼神里可以看出
Dude, this is what it's all about.
哥们 这就是你的一切
You got a woman that loves you and a place to stay.
有个爱你的女人  很好的住处
You'd be happy here, and you know it.
你在这会很幸福 你知道
Yeah, well, shacking up with Marta,
是啊 和玛特结婚
squeezing out some puppies, has its appeal, but...
养几个宝宝 有它的吸引力 可是...
this is my career.
这是我的职业
I got one shot.
我有一次机会
You're making a mistake.
你错了
You should stay right here with your lady.
你就该留在这和你的女人一起
What the fuck you gonna do
你他妈的到哥伦比亚去
in Colombia?
干啥?
Whack people,
干掉别人
program shit.
狗屁军事行动
You ain't down, fuck you.
你要是不去 干了你
Bring in my gunships
开着我的直升机
and smoke your little jungle hideaway. You know?
把丛林里的躲藏的猫都熏出来 知道不?
I mean, I'm a solider of the apocalypse, man.
伙计 我是上天封号的战士
I'll be in a chopper,
我会带着武器
door-gunning villagers and shit. Fuck 'em.
挨街挨户的射击村民
Kill the chickens and dogs, too, man.
杀死那帮坏蛋
I don't give a fuck.
我一点也不在乎
Shh, shh...
啊 啊...
Yeah.
是啊
Doce años.
12年了
- Doce años. - Doce años...
- 12年
Doce... we've been together that long.
12年 我们在一起那么久了
Es muy bonita.
她很漂亮
Man, you're bring sand to the beach, dumb ass.
你把你老婆带到派对上来 傻瓜
- Cover that shit up. - Jim, dude!
- 把那个盖起来 - 吉姆 哥们!
Huh?
哈?
How you say, um, "You're beautiful" in Spanish?
你说 "你真漂亮" 西班牙语怎么说?
Huh? "Bonita." Bonita.
哈? "Bonita." Bonita.
Come on, you don't know that shit, Toussaint?
拜托 你不懂 土沙?
Tu... bonita.
你很... bonita.
Gracias.
谢谢
Hey, baby, see my new one?
嘿 宝贝 看到我的新目标了吗?
- Right, did I get it? - Huh?
- 对 我得到她了吗? - 哈?
Think I got it?
我有机会吗?
Yeah, she got the point.
是的 她很火
Yo, Mike, that chick digs you.
迈克 那妞喜欢你
What chick?
哪个?
Oh, she's good, dog.
噢 不错
Yeah, name's Lila.
是啊 叫利娜
She's a freak. She'll fuck you, dude.
她是个怪人 她会操你
She's a freak, huh?
她是个怪人 哈?
How you know? You fuck her?
你怎么知道? 莫非你干过她?
No, out of respect for Marta.
没有 出于对玛特的尊敬
Not that I don't want... Hey, baby.
并不是不想... 嘿 宝贝
Ask her to dance.
邀她跳舞
I'm not cheating on Sylvia, dude.
我不会不忠于西尔维亚
There's a big gap between dancing and fucking, man.
跳舞和上床差的远
Go explore it.
去玩玩
No shit.
真的去了
Whoo!
唔!
No.
不
You're fucking nuts.
你疯了
You fucked up, woman.
你完了 女人
I'll do it.
我要开枪了
It's easy.
很简单
Jim!
吉姆!
What's up, man, huh?
什么事 哈?
Where's Toussaint?
土沙在哪?
He's dancing.
他在跳舞
- Yeah? - Yeah.
- 是吗? - 是
- You gonna get back
- 你会再回到
to the party? - Yeah.
派对上去吗? - 会的
Let's get back to the party, man.
我们再回到派对上去
- Yeah. - Hey, uh, go,
- 是的 - 嘿 去
go tell Toussaint that
去告诉土沙
we're gonna get the fuck out of here, man.
我们要闪人了
Just go into the party, tell him we're gonna go.
去派对里面 告诉他我们要走了
We're leaving, huh?
我们要走了 哈?
Yeah, yeah, we're gonna leave.
是的 我们要走了
Let's go, yeah?
我们走 对吗?
Yeah, let's go.
是 我们走
Go ahead, go get Toussaint, man.
去吧  去叫土沙
Go get him.
去叫他
Hey, we're going.
嘿 我们走
Come on.
拜托
Fuck you, dude.
去你的 哥们
I'm having a great time, bro.
我玩得正欢呢
Then walk back to L.A., motherfucker.
滚回洛城去 混蛋
You're in the car or not.
你上车还是不上
He's fucking crazy, man. What the fuck!
他疯了  怎么搞的
All right, let's go, man.
好了 我们走.
Hey, yo, what the fuck is your problem, psycho?!
你到底出啥毛病了 疯子?!
Hey, hey, homeboy's losing it, all right?
嘿 他神志不清 好不?
Shut the fuck up and just get in the car, all right?
闭嘴 上车 好不?
Fucking bullshit!
胡扯!
Fucked up!
完了!
Dude, dude... dude, slow down.
哥们 慢点
Fuck, man.
妈的
Whoo, yeah, man.
噢 耶
Slow down, you crazy motherfucker!
慢点 你个疯子!
I want a cop to pull me over.
我想要警察叫我停在路边
Treachery.
背叛
Jim, slow down!
吉姆  慢点!
Shut up!
闭嘴!
Fuck, dude.
妈的 哥们
Only female I trust.
只相信女人
Fuck you, God!
去你的 上帝!
You ain't got the fucking balls to take my ass.
谅你也不敢动我
Jim, don't say that shit, dude.
吉姆 别胡说
Jim!
吉姆!
Dude, you are getting out of control, okay?
你失控了 好不?
You need psychiatric help, man.
你需要心理帮助
You're seriously fucked up, dude.
你真的完了
All right, you need to sue the military or something.
好了 你必须控诉军方
You used to be mellow.
你以前很容易相处
Later, homie.
再见
'Night, dog.
晚安
Dude, I ain't hanging around you anymore
哥们 我不会再和你出去玩了
until you get some fucking help.
在你获得帮助之前
You can 12-step off, bitch.
婊子 你可以退后12步
You're dismissed.
你被开除了
He's right, dude.
他说的对
Yeah.
是的
Georgia will get me squared away.
乔治亚会使我恢复
Hope so.
希望如此
What was that shit with Marta, dude?
你和玛特怎么了?
I don't know why that happened.
我不知道发生了什么
But I'm cool. I'm cool now.
可是现在我冷静了
Okay?
好吗?
Yeah.
是啊
I'm cool.
我冷静了
Look, dude, she told me she was pregnant.
听着 她告诉我她怀孕了
I had a panic attack.
我恐慌不已
I pulled my gun.
拔出了枪
Come on, dog,
拜托
I thought you loved her, dude.
我以为你爱她
I do.
确实
God, fuck.
好 妈的
Come on, man, let's go drop off that bud.
来吧  我们把毒品放下车
What bud?
什么毒品?
There's 20 kilos in the trunk.
20千克 车后箱里
Say that again?
再说一遍?
- Of weed? - Yeah.
- 可卡因? - 是的
Get the fuck out of here, man.
见鬼了
I picked it up at the party.
我在派对上偷的
I'm dropping it at Casper's.
把它扔到卡斯朴的家
Casper's?
卡斯朴?
I get three Gs.
我有三万块了
We get three Gs.
我们有三万块了
You drove it across the border?
你装着毒品穿越边界?
Yeah.
是
What if they would've caught us?
要是他们抓住我们怎么办?
Couldn't happen, man.
不会的 哥们
My shit is on fire right now, man.
我的心着火了
My shit is wired
我现在很兴奋
You risked my ass without telling me?
你瞒着我让我冒生命危险?
That's not cool, man. For three fucking Gs?
这不好 哥们 就为了3万块?
That's... that's a good rate for transporting that.
运这个报酬丰厚
Shit, if I'd told you,
要是我告诉你的话
you would have gotten
你会在
all fucking hinkey at the border, man, gotten us nabbed.
边界露馅 我们被抓
I wouldn't have been in the fucking car, dude!
我就不会上车 哥们!
I would've been on motherfucking Greyhound.
我会坐长途巴士回家
That's a serious breach of the homie code, man,
这是严重的违法
not fuckin' telling me.
还不告诉我
I'm sorry, man. I'm sorry, you know.
对不起 兄弟 对不起
I should've had... I should've got you guys,
我真该让你们
you know, walk across the border.
走过边界
I could've met you somewhere.
再跟你们会合
But, you know, I got bills, I got shit.
可是我要钱
I gotta put my shit in storage.
我得把毒藏起来
I gotta get gas out to Georgia.
我得加油去乔治亚州
Oh, fuck your money woes, dog!
噢 去赚你妈的钱!
I am not catching a fuckin' case for you.
我不想惹官司
Let me out of the fucking car right now.
马上让我下车
Fuck, man. Come on, man, let's drop this shit off.
拜托 先去送货
Let's get paid!
去取钱!
Let me out right here.
让我出去
Mi-Mi-Mi-Mike! Listen, listen!
迈克! 听着!
Let me out right here, right now!
让我出去 马上!
You will feel so much better with a fistful of twenties.
有一撮大麻你会感觉爽很多
Huh?
哈?
Dude, we're drunk,
哥们 我们醉了
and we got a trunk full of fuckin' weed, dude, I am not...
后面有一整箱毒 我不会
Okay, fuckin', Mike, don't bitch out on me!
好了 迈克 别惹我发火!
I am still on probation, dick head.
我还在假释期
Let me out now!
让我下车!
Let me out right here right fuckin' now, dude!
让我下车 现在!
Let me get paid, will you?
先收钱好吗?
Will you fuckin' let me get paid?!
能不能让我先收钱?!
Oh, yo, get paid, man.
收钱
Fuckin' go for it, all right?
去吧 好不?
Just let me get the fuck out. I don't give a fuck, dude.
让我下车 我不在乎钱
What the fuck are you doing, man?
你在干吗?
are you doing, Jim?
你在干吗 吉姆?
What the fuck?
搞什么?
Fuck you!
去你的!
Fuck, I'm sorry, dude,
对不起
Okay? I'm sorry.
行不 对不起
Why the fuck did you put a gun to my head?
为什么用枪顶我脑袋?
Huh?
哈?
You gonna shoot me?
你要杀我?
No, man. I'm sorry. I was trippin'.
对不起 我错了
I'd never...
我从没有...
I'd never put a fuckin' gun to your head, dude
从来没有用枪顶你的脑袋
I know.
我知道
I know you wouldn't, man. I'm sorry.
我知道你不会这么做的 对不起
First your lady, now me, man. What the fuck is up?
先是你女人 现在是我 你怎么了?
I'm not thinking.
我迷糊不清
I got too much shit going on.
我脑子很乱
Oh, fuck, I'm just faded, man, that's all.
噢 我神志不清 就这样
I'm just fuckin' fade right now, okay?
我发晕了 行不?
I'll cruise you by your pad.
我送你回家
I'll drop you off, man.
我送你
I'm sorry.
对不起
Yeah. You're a fuck-up.
是啊 你干足了蠢事
I'm going with you so you don't fuck this shit up, too.
我和你一起去 免得你把这个也搞砸了
We'll go to Casper's... get the money.
我们去卡斯朴那收钱
Yeah.
是
Then you can drop me off home,
然后你可以送我回家
you can go to Georgia fed out and be the fuckin' man.
你可以去乔治亚重新做人
Yeah, I'm gonna be the fucking man.
重新做人
I can drop you off, you know.
我可以送你
Take you up the hill.
送你到山顶
No, no, no, no, no, no, no.
不
Keep on going.
继续走
Looks sketchy.
有些可疑
I don't know.
我不知道
Ho, what, you gonna shoot their pigeons?
怎么 你要杀了送钱的?
Yeah.
是
Just hurry up.
快点
Yo, Casper!
卡斯朴!
Buenos noches, señor.
你好啊 先生
¿Tiene los?cosatles?
送货吗?
Go pop the trunk, dude.
打开车箱
Con permiso.
可以交易
What's up, Casper?
你好 卡斯朴?
What up, Jim?
你好 吉姆?
What's crackin', man.
什么情况
Is that you, Mike?
是你啊 迈克?
Whassup, homes?
你好?
Yo, Casper. What up, dog?
卡斯朴 什么情况 哥们?
Nothing, homey. How you been?
没什么 你还好吗?
Still with Sylvia?
还和西尔维亚一起?
Hope so.
但愿如此
Gonna find out tonight.
今晚就可以知道
So whassup with your brother, dog?
你弟弟怎样了?
Fernie?
菲尼?
Got blasted by the hulas awhile back, ese.
被陷害了
Damn.
该死
Sorry to hear that, dog.
我很难过
You play, you pay.
玩火就要自焚
He knew what time it was.
他知道现在什么时候了
Right.
对
Hey, we gotta bounce.
我们得走了
You got the money?
拿到钱了?
Yeah, just let me check the shit, okay?
让我检查一下 行吗?
Yo, bring the feria, homey!
拿钱来!
How's your old lady?
你老婆怎么了?
Eh... bitch finally graduated, yo.
鸡婆终于毕业了
Oh, fuck it!
妈的!
Yeah, now she can support my ass, eh?
是啊 现在能养我了?
I got all the feria right here, dog.
钱都在这
It's all rolled up and shit.
都卷好了
You know what I mean?
知道我什么意思吗?
Ready to go, dog. Check this out, homes.
准备走了 检查一下钱
Ah, hell, nah!
啊 见鬼!
Yo, hold up, dog. Don't trip.
且慢 别开枪
I know these fools. They're with me, ese.
我认识他们 他们是自己人
These are the fools that jacked me, man!
这些人抢了我!
Fuck these motherfuckers! I'm shooting both of 'em!
干掉这帮混蛋! 我要打死他们!
At least give the homeboy a pass right here, dog.
至少先让这个无关的人先走
Yeah, yeah, let him bounce.
是 让他走
I don't give a fuck.
我无所谓
I want this white boy in a box, though.
我要这白人的命
Hey, you in the ride.
车上的伙计
I ever see you again, ese, you best be
要是让我再见到你 你最好
getting your last supper, 'cause you're a dead man.
吃了最后的晚餐 因为你死定了
Hey, just get the fuck outta here, Mike.
嘿 走吧 迈克
Take off, homey.
走
I'll be cool.
我没事
What the fuck?
怎么搞的?
Don't trip, ese. I'm cool.
别开枪 我没看见
Chill, dog! Chill, dog!
冷静
I got three kids...
我有三个孩子...
Oh, no, please, sir! Please!
求你了 先生 不要
- No, no, no, no, no! - Jim, no!
- 不要! - 吉姆 不要!
Please, please.
求你了
Why the fuck did you do that?
你为什么要这么做?
Pull the door!
关门!
Oh, my God, Jim!
天 吉姆!
I'm hit bad.
我被打惨了
What have we done?
我们干什么了?
I can't move my arm... and I can't feel my legs!
手不能动了 脚没感觉!
I can't move shit.
我动不了
I'm fucked up.
我完了
Okay...
好...
Don't trip...
别紧张啊...
Don't trip, dog.
别紧张
County Hospital's right there.
医院就在前面
No! No! No! County Hospital...
不! 医院
Don't you dare take me there!
别送我去!
Don't you dare!
千万不要!
I'm not going out like that.
我不能这样去
No, we're going. No, no...
不 我们去
No medical treatment.
不要医务治疗
But, but...
可是...
Mike, Mike...
迈克 迈克...
You gotta kill me.
杀了我吧
Why? Why?
为什么?
I fucked up.
我废了
Everything's shitty.
一切都没了
No, no...
不...
Mercy kill me.
求你杀了我
Ah... ah, please, mercy kill me.
求你杀我
Ah, oh, no, dude.
不 哥们
No, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no.
不
No, everything's gonna be fine.
会没事的
Jim, shh-shh, shh-shh, shh-shh, shh-shh.
吉姆
Take a look at me, you dumb fuck!
看看我 你个傻瓜!
Everything's gonna be fine?!
会没事的?!
Come on...
拜托...
You take my piece...
你拿我的枪
and you put it to my fuckin' head...
对着我的头
and you pull the trigger.
你扮动扳机
You fuckin' step up...
快点
No...
不
...and you do it.
快做
'Cause I can't.
我不能
Don't be a fuckin' pussy.
别这么娘娘腔
Oh, my God...
噢 天啊...
Don't think about it.
别想太多
Huh?
哈?
Do it.
开枪
Please.
求你了
Just kill you and bail?
杀了你然后走人?
Yeah.
对
Just take off.
走人
And don't look back...
别回头
or you'll...
否则
or you'll turn into a pillar of salt.
你会没命
Hey... Hey...
嘿
you wanted to know what it was like to kill someone.
你想尝尝杀人的滋味吗
What's up, huh?
怎么了?
No one's gonna know.
没人会知道
Hmm?
哈?
Just you...
就只有你
and just me.
我
And God.
和上帝
No fuckin' way.
不行
- Huh? - No fuckin' way.
- 啊? - 不行
You're crazy; I'm not shootin' you, dog.
你疯了 我不杀你
It's mercy, dog.
行行好
It's mercy.
成全我
I deserve that.
我罪有应得
I'd do it for you.
换成我 我会打死你的
Yeah.
是啊
Take it.
拿着
Yeah, yeah.
是
JIM Yeah, yeah... yeah...
吉姆
D-Don't, don't think about it.
别想太多
Yeah, yeah...
是
Ah... ah...
啊
You did this to yourself, you stupid fuck!
是你自找的 白痴!
You're always doing stupid shit!
你总是做蠢事!
- I gotta fuckin' fix it! - Okay, okay.
- 我要杀你! - 好 好
Is that what you fuckin' want?!
那是你想要的吗？!
- Yes. - Huh?
- 是的 - 哈?
You want me to fuckin' fix your head,
你要我毙了你
- once and for all?! - Come on, it's easy.
- 彻底了结你吗?! - 来呀 很容易
It's easy. No! Bullshit!
很容易 不! 胡说!
Bullshit! Not for me!
胡说! 对我来说太难了!
I love you, fuckin' shit bag.
我爱你 混蛋
I love you, too.
我也是
I'm gonna miss you, brother.
我会想你的 兄弟
I'm sorry.
对不起
- Everything's gonna be okay. - Yeah.
- 会没事的 - 对
Yeah.
对
I know.
我知道